<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><root><magazine>Cosmopolitan</magazine><frequency>Monthly</frequency><edition>'Men need to compete all the time'</edition><items><section name="Centre Spread"><article><headline>'Men need to compete all the time'</headline><byline>Lizzi Hosking</byline><introtext>Here, in an exclusive interview with Cosmo, Jessica Alba reveals the truth about friendship, fame, fidelity, and her family. Read on. </introtext><bodytext><p><strong> </strong>Kid Rock once said, 'If you have a problem with the paparazzi, move to Michigan,'" says Jessica Alba over a salad at the Polo Lounge in LA's Beverly Hills Hotel. "And it's true. But my husband's business is here. My family are here. If we moved any further out I'd literally never see him. He works, like, nine to seven as it is."<br /><br />Yesterday, the 28-year-old was chased to the<em> Cosmo</em> cover shoot in Hollywood's Siren Studios. The reason? She's found herself smack bang in the middle of paparazzi hell, after the rumour recently surfaced that her husband of nearly two years, producer Cash Warren, has been locking lips with Lindsay Lohan. But like a true <em>Cosmo </em>girl, she refuses to let it get her down. <br /><br />"It's so ridiculous," she says. "But I guess when you're boring like me and you're just a regular mum and a regular friend, people want to turn you into something more notorious and fabulous. I'm just not. I think that's what's disappointing."<br /><br />Jessica looks amazingly low-key in jeans and a chunky-knit cardi and is so down-to-earth and normal that it would be easy to forget while talking to her that she's racked up a string of hit movies such as <em>Fantastic Four</em>, <em>Sin City </em>and <em>The Eye</em>. Easy to forget, that is, until this exchange takes place... <br /><br /><strong>Woman: "Sorry to interrupt, I just wanted to say hello."<br />Jessica: </strong>"Paula! How are you? [They chat, hug, then Jessica sits back down.] That was Paula Wagner. She was Tom Cruise's agent, then she ran his company and United Artists. Actually, she started off as an actress. And now she's a powerhouse. A cool lady. Where were we?" <br /><br />Here, in an exclusive interview with <em>Cosmo</em>, Jessica reveals the truth about friendship, fame, fidelity, and her family. <br /><br /><strong>Welcome back to Cosmo! Last time we spoke in 2008, you'd recently got married and given birth to your daughter, Honor marie. So, how's it all going?<br /></strong>"It's really great, thank you."<br /><br /><strong>So, tell us about your husband...<br /></strong>"We're similar in some ways and opposites in others. We're both open in social situations. But he's not crazy about movies and I am. He doesn't like cooking and I do. He loves sport and I don't."<br /><br /><strong>Yeah, that's pretty universal...<br /></strong>"Men need to compete all the time. I can be competitive, but it's with myself... Anyway, he helps me sit back, think and assess the situation. On the flip side, I can work 18 hours a day and then go home and be a mum and cook dinner for six people and he would never do that! <strong> </strong></p><p><strong> You've always been independent. Was it hard to do the love, honour and obey thing?<br /></strong>"I didn't. I had a hard time agreeing with marriage at all because I feel like it's been warped. Originally it was two families coming together to make a stronger family. It was about survival &mdash; not love or soulmates. And it wasn't until the last, what, 100 years that we've put this onus on marriage being about finding your soulmate. And now, the way they market marriage is that it's all about Prince Charming sweeping you off your feet. I didn't agree with any of that. This tradition of obeying your husband like he's king? It's a load of crap. Love and honour, yes. But you should love and honour yourself too, and your friends."<br /><br /><strong>Why did you get married then?<br /></strong>"I chose to get married because, essentially, you're given a deck of cards in life. The hand you were dealt is your family and you can't choose them. But the one person you can choose to bring into your life as your family and to have that unconditional love with is your husband or wife."<br /><br /><strong>You have to keep working at it though, so it's not unconditional...<br /></strong>"You do have to keep working at it, yes, and constantly. You can't have a great relationship unless you're both coming to the table and both sweeping each other off your feet. That was the greatest lesson my parents told me. They said, 'If you're fighting and it's difficult or you're not happy before you get married, it's only going to get worse. So before you get married and have kids, this has to be the time of your life." </p><p><strong>The tabloids have been rife with rumours of your husband's alleged infidelity. How does that make you feel?<br /></strong>"When people wrote lies about me before I had Honor, I'd get upset or I'd get nauseous or I'd get angry or I'd want revenge. Now, it's like, it's just so ridiculous and it's not even close to being the truth. I know who I am, and I know that I love my family and I love my kid and that being a good mum is my numberone priority."<br /><br /><strong>So what's your tactic for dealing with this rumour about Cash and Lindsay Lohan?<br /></strong>"And the one about me and Mario Lopez [a US TV star]? I don't even know him very well. The last time I saw him, by the way, was at Eva Longoria's wedding and I was pregnant!" <strong> </strong></p><p><strong> You must have a way of dealing with it&mdash;we know we'd find it impossible to ignore...<br /></strong>"He's like, 'Did you hear this?' or, 'Someone told me that.' We hear it from our friends too, or my publicist. But it's all lies." <br /><br /><strong>We celebrate friends in Cosmo. What do you have to say about yours?<br /></strong>"I've known my group of girlfriends since I was 15 &mdash; my cousin is one of them so we grew up together. And I have a group of mum friends &mdash; some I met during pregnancy and some after. It's easier to hang with mum friends because your kid can have a meltdown and you don't have to apologise! I have a baby music class at my house every Monday morning at 10 a.m. and I make organic pastries. I really like making my friends feel special. The qualities I look for in a friend? Easy-going and loyal. And you need someone who has your back." <br /><br /><strong>You've got a film with Lindsay coming out this year, too...<br /></strong>"Yeah, and my husband may do a TV show with her &mdash; ironically, about the ridiculousness of tabloids.<br /><br /><strong>Have you spoken to Lindsay?<br /></strong>"Yeah, and she's really nice. We hang out and chat for hours.<br /><br /><strong>You seem so sorted, but you've said that you weren't confident when you were growing up.<br /></strong>"The mentality in my family was always if you weren't good enough, you strive to be better. So if you ever felt like you were good enough, that was the end of the road. My grandparents met during the Depression and that's just the way they operated. But ironically my parents always told me I was doing a good job. They'd give me over-thetop compliments. As a kid, I was embarrassed. It's only now I realise that really is how you feel with your kids. Now, everything Honor does is just the greatest ever!"<br /><br /><strong>You missed a lot of school due to health problems. How did that affect you?<br /></strong>"I had bad asthma so every time I got a cold, I got pneumonia and would have to be hospitalised. I'd miss school so did all of my work from the hospital. I ended up finishing my school work early and got straight As, so then got bored when I was in class. I spent a lot of time alone and daydreamed a lot. I didn't have any friends &mdash; not really." <strong> </strong></p><p><strong> When did you learn to like yourself&mdash;or are there still things you want to change?<br /></strong>"I used to harp on about my insufficiencies, but after I had Honor I forgave myself for not being perfect. Having kids puts everything into perspective."<br /><br /><strong>Do women in Hollywood stick together or is there a lot of rivalry?<br /></strong>"Everybody's different. I've never wanted someone else's career. I just wanted to be myself and to hopefully be a role model, particularly to minorities and to women who don't fit into the box."<br /><br /><strong>What's your attitude towards equality?<br /></strong>"I believe there's going to be more equality, and if women take on the attitude of lifting each other up instead of being competitive with each other, it'll be better for all of us. There are amazing actresses&mdash; Zoe Saldana, Drew Barrymore, Julia Robert s , Jessica Biel , Eva Mendes &mdash; so I'm all about supporting each other instead of stepping on each other to succeed. I was focussed on making money and trying to stay relevant. But now I want to play women who are strong and independent, who are completely flawed and have problems but that's really okay."<br /><br /><strong>What about equality in relationships?<br /></strong>"Men and women are equal as we balance each other. In many ways, men have to prove their love to their family through work, whereas women take care of the house. One isn't greater than the other. And you should both be vulnerable. If either feels you can't show that you're overwhelmed, that's not equal. Men are allowed to have breakdowns just as much."</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article></section><section name="Confessions"><article><headline>Sloppy Seconds</headline><byline></byline><introtext>I hooked up with my buddy's ex. When he found out, the first thing he said to me was 'You know she has an STD, right?' I freaked out...</introtext><bodytext><p>"I hooked up with my buddy's ex. When he found out, the first thing he said to me was 'You know she has an STD, right?' I freaked out and confronted her. She denied it and I told her she was a lying bitch. I visited the doc and after a painful check-up, I realised my buddy was just trying to get back at me for sleeping with his ex.  <br />&mdash; <em>Hank, 25</em></p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Panty Flasher</headline><byline></byline><introtext>I hadn't done laundry in a while, so I wore the only clean underwear I had: an ultratight thong. It was really uncomfortable...</introtext><bodytext><p>"I hadn't done laundry in a while, so I wore the only clean underwear I had: an ultratight thong. It was really uncomfortable, so in the middle of the day, I took it off. Since the pants I was wearing that day didn't have any pockets, I stuffed it into one of my boots. Later, I stopped by a shoe store. As a cute salesman was helping me out, I took off my boot and the thong fell out onto the floor right in front of him! I didn't know what to do, so I stuffed it back in my boot as quickly as possible, put it on my foot, and ran out of the store." <br />&mdash; <em>Nora, 34 </em></p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article></section><section name="Love & Lust"><article><headline>Guys are more fearful of wedding than marriage</headline><byline></byline><introtext>My boyfriend and I got engaged a couple of months ago and I've noticed  that as our wedding planning has gotten more intense, his sex drive has  gone down.</introtext><bodytext><p><strong>My boyfriend and I got engaged a couple of months ago and I've noticed that as our wedding planning has gotten more intense, his sex drive has gone down. I'm doing most of the work, so I feel like I should be the one stressed out and not in the mood. He's not getting cold feet in any other way, so what's the deal?<br /></strong>Most engaged guys are way more fearful of the wedding than they are of being married, in part because planning is a gigantic effort that they typically have next to no control over. And dudes aren't real fond of being totally out of control. For instance, your fiance may say he doesn't care about the flowers and he probably doesn't, but it's easy for a guy to see how consumed you and others are with decisions like that and then start feeling like he's the least important thing in his own wedding. Ask your guy to be more involved in the planning and see how he reacts. He might appreciate the gesture. Make sure he knows how much you're looking forward to being his wife, not how much you're looking forward to being a bride.</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Talk about your feelings</headline><byline></byline><introtext> I've been dating a guy for several months. It was clear that we  weren't seeing other people</introtext><bodytext><p><strong>I've been dating a guy for several months. It was clear that we weren't seeing other people...or so I thought, because I just discovered that he slept with someone else. He claims it wasn't cheating because we aren't in a relationship. But is it?<br /></strong>I think you gave him a free pass to fool around with other chicks. You never actually talked about being a committed couple, so he was able to justify doing whatever he wanted. Is that sleazy? Of course. It's like a murderer getting off on a technicality. But becoming monogamous is a milestone and you can't just assume you've reached it without having a talk. Good luck working it out.</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Are they really my good friends?</headline><byline></byline><introtext> I recently broke up with my boyfriend of six years.</introtext><bodytext><p><strong>I recently broke up with my boyfriend of six years. Since then, my platonic guy friends are all flirting with me a lot more, and a couple have flat-out suggested that we hook up. Were they ever really my friends to begin with?<br /></strong>Six years would be an awfully long time to hang around if they'd only wanted to do you. I think their behaviour actually proves that they're good friends: they found you attractive before you were single, yet they didn't make a move because you had a boyfriend. Look, guys can be extremely shortsighted when it comes to sex. All they're able to process is that a hot chick is suddenly single after being off-limits for years. You can send a clear message that you're not interested in hooking up as long as you're careful of their feelings. Shrug it off and even laugh about it. That way, their egos won't be bruised and you'll keep your dude friends.<br /><br /> </p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>8 ways to feel closer after sex</headline><byline></byline><introtext>Our strategies help you ride the warm, fuzzy high. </introtext><bodytext><p>Take a moment to think about what you and your guy usually do after sex. Chances are, it's sleep, eat, or flip on the TV. Not exactly romantic, especially considering that the few hours afterwards are one of the best times to bond. "When you orgasm, hormones are released that make you feel more connected,  says clinical sexologist Rachael Ross, M.D., Ph.D. "Take advantage of that by doing things to prolong the feeling.  But that doesn't mean intense conversations or eye gazing&mdash;little gestures can reap big benefits. Try these tips with your man tonight. <br /><br /><strong> 1.</strong> If you're hungry, forgo ordering a pizza and instead break out red wine and cheese. It will continue the sensual vibe you had going and the antioxidants in the vino will increase blood flow, relaxing both of you.<br /><br /><strong>2.</strong> Upgrade your usual post-sex shower by giving each other neck rubs. the bonding hormones oxytocin and prolactin that are released when you climax are also triggered by touch, so the massage will extend the feelings of closeness. <br /><br /><strong>3.</strong> Instead of rolling over once the action is done, drape one of your legs over his and rest your hands on his chest. It will keep you connected without doing the spooning thing. <br /><br /><strong>4.</strong> Before you get busy, turn off anything with an on button, like your cellphones, laptops, and tV. that way, the only thing you'll be plugged into afterwards is each other, not your facebook news feed or the latest lost episode. <br /><br /><strong>5.</strong> Play hooky and call in sex&mdash;er, sick after your romp. Having to leave ASAP, whether it's to meet a friend for brunch or attend your can't-miss yoga class is a total mood killer. Reschedule your plans and enjoy a leisurely hour or two of doing nothing together in bed.</p><p><strong><br />6.</strong> One word: candles. light a few after you hook up (instead of before) and the mood will instantly feel more romantic.  </p><table border="1" cellspacing="5" cellpadding="5" width="200" align="right"><tbody><tr><td><p><strong>Bonding bonus: </strong>Connecting with  another person boosts the level of the hormone progesterone, reducing  stress.</p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><strong><br />7.</strong> Reverse-strip each other. Slowly button his shirt and let him zip up your skirt. Dressing each other is super-intimate since it taps in to the primal instinct to 'preen' your mate. <br /><br /><strong>8.</strong> Set your iPod to a romantic playlist. choose tunes that remind you of your favourite moments together (like a concert you went to). Just listening to them will make you two feel closer without having to speak.</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>The new marriage age rule matters</headline><byline></byline><introtext>We doubt you were shocked when Avril Lavigne recently announced she was splitting from her husband of three years.</introtext><bodytext><p>We doubt you were shocked when Avril Lavigne recently announced she was splitting from her husband of three years. But while it's tempting to assume the cause was her bratty persona or rocker lifestyle, comments from her friends suggested that something more universal was at play: she was only 21 when she tied the knot and later told pals that she realised she'd been too young to make such a life-altering decision. Could fellow young celebrity divorcees Reese Witherspoon, Kate Hudson, and Britney Spears have also hit the same age-related issue?<br /><br />The latest research indicates it's more than likely. According to recent statistics from the Department of Health and Human Services, US, women who wed in their late teens or early 20s are more likely to be divorced in 10 years than those who wait until 25 or older. What is it about 25 that ups your chances of having a lasting romance? Experts say it's all about what you've spent those years doing.<br /><strong><br />The magic number</strong><br />There are practical reasons for the mid-20s dividing line, and most of them boil down to two biggies: education and money. Turns out, the more years of higher education a woman has under her belt on her wedding day, the lower the chances that she'll get divorced...and by 25, you're more likely to have earned a degree or two. "Educated women tend to be more confident about who they are and less willing to settle for a man who doesn't meet their standards,  explains Terri Orbuch, Ph.D., author of Five Simple Steps To Take Your Marriage From Good To Great.<br /><br />But the marriage-related benefits of working and having money of your own go beyond feeling secure, says Pepper Schwartz, Ph.D., author of Finding Your Perfect Match. Learning to budget your cash carefully when you're single will help you avoid financial problems&mdash; one of the main causes of couple fights&mdash;for the rest of your life. And juggling responsibilities, dealing with differing personalities, and resolving conflicts on the job force you to develop skills that are necessary for maintaining long-term love.<br /><strong><br />Knowing the real you</strong><br />At 25, you've had time for some crucial life experiences, including a relationship or two that may have improved your Mr Right radar. "You've probably dated enough to have a better idea of what you don't want in a man,  says Orbuch. Perhaps the most important aspect of waiting is that you'll know what your goals and values really are, says Paul Coleman, Psy.D., author of The Complete Idiot's Guide To Intimacy. It's not like it's a given that your marriage won't survive. But given the choice, you might consider putting off the big day until your mid-20s or later.</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Does your man have a solo-sex problem?</headline><byline>Bethany Heitman</byline><introtext>More guys are secretly going overboard with self-pleasuring. Keep reading to find out if your boyfriend's habit is getting out of hand. </introtext><bodytext><p>There's breaking news in "guy world : many committed guys are treating themselves to a little too much one-handed fun, and it could leave both of you feeling less than satisfied in bed. To get the scoop, we talked to top sex experts and found out exactly why this is happenin' and what you can do about it.<br /><strong><br />What the hell is going on?</strong><br />"There are two current factors that are leading more and more men to develop masturbation dependencies, which is when someone masturbates so frequently that it interferes with a healthy sex life,  says sex therapist Ian Kerner, Ph.D., author of She Comes First. And rest assured, neither of them have anything to do with you. "First, the bad economy is leaving a lot of guys without jobs, so they sit at home, bored, and start masturbating more often,  says Kerner.<br /><br />"And second, porn has become so accessible that guys can watch something new every day, so a compulsion grows. There are actually serious consequences to all that whacking off: if he's doing it too often, he may stop being able to climax with you. "A man's hand can provide a lot more friction than a vagina, and if he's compulsively masturbating, he may grow so used to that intense friction that anything less won't do it for him,  says Kerner.<br /><br /><strong>How to get him unhooked</strong><br />If you've noticed that your guy takes a long time to climax during sex or if he can't finish at all, the only way to find out if excessive solo sex is the problem is to ask. "Tell him he's seemed dissatisfied during sex and you want to make sure he's enjoying himself,  says Kerner. Then mention that you read in Cosmo that masturbating too much can make it hard to orgasm. By bringing up that you read this article, you'll let him know he's not the only one doing it, which will make him more willing to talk about it. Often guys need company, even if figuratively, when any of their man-habits are under the microscope. The awareness that this isn't a problem just in your head but other girlfriends are going through the same thing will also make it easier for him to sorta, kinda try and make it up to you.<br /><br />Once you've gotten it out in the open, the best course of action is for him simply to stop cold turkey. Motivate him by explaining that sex is better for you when he's able to finish and that you're open to having sex with him more often. Hearing that his habit is getting in the way of your enjoyment should kick his ass into gear, because guys take pride in being able to please you. Though if he still doesn't stop, he could need professional help.<br /><br />"If he is resistant, he may need to seek out the help of a therapist,  says certified sex therapist Annette Demby, who specialises in compulsive sexual behaviour. Over time, he'll get used to climaxing during sex again and be able to go back to masturbating with a normal frequency, as long as he's not doing so multiple times a day.</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>How to meet the perfect man</headline><byline>Ky Henderson</byline><introtext>Believe it or not, but Your crew can grant you access to scores of new cuties. But first, give them a little nudge. </introtext><bodytext><p>What if we told you there's a 70 percent chance that someone in your social circle knows your future husband? No doubt you'd be on high alert the next time you're out. Well, keep your eyes open, because a study of married couples showed 7 out of 10 met through mutual acquaintances.<br /><br />"Because we tend to associate with people similar to us, we end up having things in common with even friends of friends of friends,  says James Fowler, Ph.D., who cites the study in his book Connected: The Surprising Power Of Our Social Networks And How They Shape Our Lives.<br /><br />Unfortunately for us, knowledge is not power. You have to get out there and mingle. Here's how!<br /><strong><br />Describe Mr Right</strong><br />When it comes to your love life, being pushy can help. "You have to tell your friends that you're on the lookout  says psychologist and dating coach Barbara Cox, Ph.D., who points out a bonus: "Verbalising your desires actually helps form a firmer idea of what you want. <br /><br />No matter how detailed you make your description of Mr Right, introducing you to a boy is not high up on a pal's agenda. So if a friend insists you couldn't be interested in any of the single guys she knows, don't take her word for it, says Evan Marc Katz, coauthor of Why You're Still Single. Get yourself an invite when they hang out, and check them out.<br /><br /><strong>Stick to Groups </strong><br />Big group outings are the best way to meet guys at the edge of your social circle "If you don't get along with a guy, there's no pressure to keep talking to him,  Cox says. And if you're out with people you're at ease with, chances are you're going to be charming, and at your best.<br /><br />Another great idea: throw a party, ask every friend to bring a person of the opposite sex. At worst, you'll make a few more friends. "The more new friends you make, the more eligible guys you meet,  says professional matchmaker Janis Spindel, author of How To Date Men.<br /><br /><strong>Get Online </strong><br />"Facebook gives you access to an otherwise untapped pool of men.  Fowler says. Shamelessly browse for hot guys in friends' photos. If you find one, ask the common friend for an intro ASAP.</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Habits of crazy-in-love couples</headline><byline>Carrie Sloan</byline><introtext>With iconic couples breaking up left and night-no-more Reese and Jake-it's easy to think the odds are stacked against happily ever after. But plenty of relationships stay strong and steamy forever, and yours can too. </introtext><bodytext><p>We've uncovered the secrets to being that couple&mdash; you know, the been-together-forever pair who are so connected, they make the Obamas' relationship look tentative. Granted, you have to have the same values when it comes to things like kids and marriage, but there are other, more surprising factors at play. "Many couples think staying tight requires magical soul-mate status, but in reality, the trick is to establish habits that strengthen your bond,  says Yvonne Thomas, Ph.D., a psychologist in Los Angeles,US.<br /><br />We interviewed a team of relationship experts, including Thomas, and pinpointed exactly what those habits are. From the right way to make up after a fight to how often you talk about the future, using these strategies on a regular basis will keep your love going strong forever...or for as long as you want it to. Find it hard to believe? Read on to discover the secrets that your so-in-love neighbour/best friend/sister/co-worker has internalised. The best part&mdash;your love life will be completely shock-proof after this.<br /><br /><strong>Other women see Ben stiller, you see Ben affleck </strong><br />One of the biggest secrets to long-lasting lust is also the easiest: tweaking the way you think so that you always try to see the best in your guy...and helping him to do the same.<br /><br />We're not suggesting that you ignore his mistakes or pretend he's being sweet when he's acting like an ass. It's more about reframing your view so you appreciate all the great things he has going for him. For example, if he's so devoted to his job that you feel like you two barely talk some nights, resist the urge to gripe. Instead, think about how much you respect his passion and ambition. If you're the one working overtime, remind him of how much he loves to brag about his ultra-accomplished girlfriend or wife.<br /><br />Besides squashing resentment, focussing on what draws you to each other will revive that gotta-have-younow lust you had in the beginning. "When starting to date, all couples have an idealised take on each other, which leads to intense attraction,  says Thomas. "But after six months to a year, that often fades and we tend to zero in on what exactly is wrong with the other person. <br /><br />Fixating on faults can make you dissatisfied in the relationship. Make your union strong by always being aware of how lucky you both are.<br /><br /><strong>You keep your fights clean</strong><br />Conventional wisdom has it that partners who always (or rarely) duke it out are on thin relationship ice. But it's how you fight that matters, not how often. "Conflict is inevitable, but nasty behaviour, like finger-pointing and name-calling, shows contempt for each other, and that's sulphuric acid for love,  says relationship researcher John Gottman, Ph.D., co-founder of the Gottman Institute in Seattle, US. On the flip side, if you confront problems head-on and in a way that conveys respect, you can actually get closer during a fight. "Research shows that the most successful couples use something called the soft start-up when they argue,  says Gottman. Say your guy suddenly bailed on meeting you and your friends for dinner one night. Instead of blurting out "You're a total douche bag for not showing up!  go with "Hey, what happened? I was upset that you cancelled like that.  Or if you're the one who screwed up big, defuse his fury by saying "I can understand why you'd be mad.  That cooperative, rather than combative, approach will help transform a fight into a conversation.<br /><br />And if one of you does fly off the handle (which is bound to happen every once in a while), do damage control as soon as possible. Make genuine repair attempts: Apologise, then laugh or touch him to cut the tension, says Gottman. These actions tell the other person that, no matter what you disagree about, you're still on the same team.<br /><br /><strong>You share the same badass habits </strong><br />Sneaking into posh hotel pools after hours, e-mailing your friends-and-family discount to everyone and their mother, calling in sick and downloading Xbox game demos all day&mdash;hey, everyone has one or two ways that they break the rules or behave badly. But the surprising news is that whether you and your guy agree on which infractions are okay&mdash;and which ones aren't&mdash;has a direct impact on the longevity of your relationship. <br /><br />This is especially true when it comes to seriously bad-for-you behaviours. A State University of New York at Buffalo study found that couples who mirrored each other's levels of drinking and smoking stayed close as time went by, while abstainers paired with smokers and/or drinkers eventually split. <br /><br />Booze and cigarettes aside, having harmless guilty pleasures in common also helps your love go the long haul. "If you can both be a little reckless in certain areas of your life&mdash;but within boundaries you each find appropriate&mdash;it can feel exciting, like you have a partner in crime,  says Thomas. So go ahead and be bad together&mdash;just make sure you don't end up cuddling in the back of a police cruiser.<br /><br /><strong>You satisfy each other's naughty needs </strong><br />As you know, lots of superhot, burn-ahole-in-the-bed booty does wonders when it comes to deepening your connection. That's no problem during the first months of your relationship; your bodies are brand-new to each other, and you're always looking for reasons to be naked and horizontal. But after a while, your true bedroom personalities begin to reveal themselves...and it becomes even more crucial that you stay aware of what the other person craves.<br /><br />"There are two basic sexual types: thrill seekers and comfort seekers,  says sex therapist Ian Kerner, PhD, author of She Comes First. Thrill seekers crave novelty; they get bored easily and are always looking for ways to amp up things. Comfort seekers, on the other hand, may like getting busy a lot and could be turned on by some out-there things, "but the routine is key,  explains Kerner. "Whatever they like, they want to stick with; they don't have that drive thrill seekers have to constantly test out new scenarios. <br /><br />If you both happen to be the same type, keeping each other satisfied will come more naturally. But if you and your guy are opposites, it can still work&mdash;as long as you make communicating about sex a habit, says Kerner.<br /><br /><strong>You both pack endless surprises </strong><br />Uncovering new details about each other, like finding out that he starred in his seventh-grade musical or letting it slip that you can count to 20 in Japanese, triggers the release of the neurotransmitter dopamine, which leads to that isn't he/she so awesome feeling.<br /><br />"Partners who last aren't static,  says Thomas. "They continually reveal different facets of themselves. <br /><br />It can be as simple as doing novel activities together, like trying Korean food or the opera just for the hell of it&mdash;even if you both hate it, you'll still learn something new about each other. You also can ask questions about your pasts or what you'd like to do in the future. "Doing so will keep that exciting first stage of a relationship&mdash;when you're slowly peeling away layers of who you both are&mdash;alive and ongoing,  says Gottman. That perpetual newness is the drug that will keep you high on each other forever... and ever. So what are you waiting for? Master these moves and be a rock-steady twosome till eternity.<br /><br /><strong>The love ritual that keeps us tight</strong><br />We asked readers how they reinforce their connection (in ways that don't involve getting naked).<br /><br />When we first moved into our new apartment, we didn't have a table for a couple of weeks. So my boyfriend and I would put a blanket on the floor and have nightly 'picnics.' We have a table now, but we still like to set up picnics in the living room, complete with takeout sandwiches and a bottle of our favourite wine. It's sort of a reminder of how far we've come.  <br /><em>&mdash;Felicia, 28</em><br /><br />We live in different cities, so we've developed this thing where we will book a hotel room and have a staycation in either Baltimore, where he lives, or New York, where I live. No roommates, no family members...just me, him, and some serious quality time.  <br /><em>&mdash;Jessica, 23</em><br /><br />My husband and I play Iron Chef once a month. We pick a new theme each time, then create meals centred around it. The competition heats us both up and the sex rocks.  <br /><em>&mdash;Holly, 31</em><br /><br />Every Friday night, we get cosy in our sweats and watch all the TV shows we DVRed from that past week. It's our downtime when we really get to enjoy each other oneon-one and relax after the stresses from the week.  <br /><em>&mdash;Michelle, 25</em></p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>50 fun ways to fire up your love</headline><byline>Korin Miller</byline><introtext>Whether you flash him a peek at your ta-tas on the sly or attempt to re-enact dance show routines in your living room, these silly moves will bring you infinitely closer as a couple.</introtext><bodytext><p>You wouldn't think that goofing off with your guy would make you fall harder for each other, but kidding around has surprisingly romantic side effects. "Inside jokes and playful behaviour draw a couple together because they provide a quick emotional high,  says relationship therapist Paul Coleman, Psy.D., author of The Complete Idiot's Guide To Intimacy. "That high makes you feel excited about each other, strengthening your connection and keeping things fresh. <br /><br />Of course, things won't stay fresh for long if you keep having the same kind of fun over and over. Enter our list of creative, inane, and often highly seductive activities. You might make some messes and shock a few strangers, but you'll both be too love-struck to care.<br /><br /><strong>1.</strong> Emblazon a close-up of your bra-covered boobs and his boxer-clad package on mugs.<br /><br /><strong>2.</strong> Go commando together for the day (it'll be your little secret).<br /><br /><strong>3.</strong> Spell out "I want you  with kitchen magnets.<br /><br /><strong>4.</strong> Send sexy texts to each other when you're at the same party.<br /><br /><strong>5.</strong> Celebrate with wine on a Sunday.<br /><br /><strong>6.</strong> Ask him to lotion you up in the morning before work&mdash;just leave extra time for the inevitably lusty results.<br /><br /><strong>7. </strong>Draw a map of your place, and pinpoint where you've gotten it on. Then write in the spots you still want to break in.<br /><br /><strong>8. </strong>Take a shower together, doing everything for him, like washing his hair and scrubbing him all over&mdash;then trade off.<br /><br /><strong>9.</strong> Tune in to a travel channel special one night and make a theme dinner to match.<br /><br /><strong>10.</strong> Pop into a snooker bar after work a few times and learn how to play. Then challenge him to a game.<br /><br /><strong>11.</strong> Do a hilarious karaoke duet, like "Single Ladies,  by Beyonce.<br /><br /><strong>12.</strong> Make snowballs with ice and store them in your freezer for summer fun.<br /><br /><strong>13.</strong> Draw an outline of your naked body on his shower wall with a soap crayon.<br /><br /><strong>14.</strong> Have a triathlon date, competing in pizza eating, thumb wars, and leg wrestling.<br /><br /><strong>15.</strong> Try to out-cheese each other with funny love notes, like "Some bunny loves you. <br /><br /><strong>16.</strong> Set up private Twitter pages and post naughty messages each other all day.<br /><br /><strong>17.</strong> Work up a competitive sweat with a sesh at the gym.<br /><br /><strong>18. </strong>Use Rock, Paper, Scissors to decide pressing arguments, like what to watch on TV.<br /><br /><strong>19.</strong> Form senseless but fun road-trip traditions, like never not stopping for him to pee.<br /><br /><strong>20.</strong> Have cocktail night once a month, and try new recipes.<br /><br /><strong>21. </strong>Guess what your dog's up to during the workday, then find out with a pet's-eye-view camera.<br /><br /><strong>22. </strong>Gift him a colouring book featuring you naked. You can make one using Photoshop or an Epson printer.<br /><br /><strong>23. </strong>Hit a thrift store, and buy outfits for each other. Then wear them out that night.<br /><br /><strong>24. </strong>Play naughty-word jumble (e-n-p-s-i) via text message when you're bored in line.<br /><br /><strong>25. </strong>Leave a sexy note in the shower that reads "Meet me back here after work. <br /><br /><strong>26. </strong>Make up aliases and stick with them all night.<br /><br /><strong>27.</strong> Bake his fave childhood treat (ask his mom for the recipe).<br /><br /><strong>28.</strong> Create a new Facebook account just for the two of you.<br /><br /><strong>29.</strong> Have hour-long dance-offs at home.<br /><br /><strong>30.</strong> Pick ridiculous ringtones for each other.<br /><br /><strong>31. </strong>Write down funny things each of you say, then vote on which quote is the most hilarious.<br /><br /><strong>32. </strong>Flick your favourite photos of each other back and forth on your iPhones using the Mover app.<br /><br /><strong>33. </strong>Flash him when no one else is looking.<br /><br /><strong>34.</strong> Make up stories about other people while waiting in line.<br /><br /><strong>35.</strong> Look at pricey real-estate ads, and debate which property you'd "buy. <br /><strong><br />36. </strong>Try to throw as many cliched song lyrics into your conversation as possible, like "You are the wind beneath my wings. <br /><strong><br />37. </strong>Text one word at a time to each other until you come up with a sentence.<br /><br /><strong>38.</strong> Bake naughty shaped cookies, using your bodies as inspiration.<br /><br /><strong>39.</strong> Write reminders in his BlackBerry calendar on the sly, like "Ravage Tanya tonight. <br /><br /><strong>40.</strong> Do a Skype striptease in the next room, and see how long you can stay apart.<br /><br /><strong>41. </strong>Just flip through our sex manual from previous issues and try the positions.<br /><br /><strong>42.</strong> Flip through a Victoria's Secret catalogue together and see who can make the swarthiest pirate by drawing eye patches, goatees, hats, etc., on the models.<br /><br /><strong>43.</strong> Join a weekend football team and feel each other up midgame.<br /><strong><br />44. </strong>Teach your dog a cool new trick together after watching Animal Planet's Superfetch.<br /><br /><strong>45. </strong>Hide a fake tattoo on your body and challenge him to find it.<br /><br /><strong>46. </strong>Eat out on Sunday&mdash;for breakfast, lunch, and dinner.<br /><br /><strong>47.</strong> Build a sled out of stuff at your place. Hint: Aluminum foil&ndash;covered cookie sheets work wonders.<br /><br /><strong>48.</strong> Hold shirts-versus-skins bed wrestling and flip a coin to decide who's wearing what.<br /><br /><strong>49.</strong> Initiate a Top Chef quick-fire challenge cook-off using only ingredients found in your kitchen.<br /><br /><strong>50.</strong> Declare an all-out poking war on Facebook. <br /><strong><br />Well, that didn't work<br /><br />These readers had the right idea&mdash; until their sexy plans totally bombed.</strong><br /><br />"I bought a belly-dancing outfit, turned on some exotic music, and attempted to give my guy a sexy striptease. But all he did was laugh hysterically at the show&mdash;for the next 10 minutes. I burst into tears and locked myself in the bathroom until he apologised.  <br /><em>&mdash;Julie, 29</em><br /><br />"I went to a happy hour and, on my way home, texted my BF to meet me at my apartment...but I passed out as soon as I hit the couch! He lived a 20-minute drive away and just sat in my parking garage for an hour, thinking I'd finally pick up my phone. I never did.  <br /><em>&mdash;Elizabeth, 27</em><br /><br />"I once mailed my man some homemade chocolate-chip cookies with a note that read, 'Share with your roommates!' Too bad I had accidentally switched the proportions of sugar and salt so they were really salty and gross. His friends nicknamed me the Demon Baker.  <br /><em>&mdash;Tara, 28</em><br /><br />"I sent my guy some racy pics one night, but an hour later, he still hadn't gotten them. Turns out, I'd sent them to the wrong number, and the next day, I got a call from the police about indecent exposure! I had accidentally sent them to a middle-age woman, who freaked out. Luckily, she thought it was funny and decided not to press charges when she heard what really happened.  <br /><em>&mdash;Ebony, 21<br /><br />Sources: Paul Coleman, Psy.D; relationship expert Seth Meyers, Ph.D.</em></p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Why he's so turned on by...</headline><byline></byline><introtext>There's no such thing as too much of a good thing.</introtext><bodytext><p>There's no such thing as too much of a good thing.</p><p><strong>Hot twin sisters</strong><br />There's no such thing as too much of a good thing. Plus, the thought of them making out is totally twisted...and smokin'.<br /><br /><strong>Librarians</strong><br />They're supposed to be buttoned-up and uptight. So if he could turn one into a wild sex goddess, that would make him a sex god.<br /><br /><strong>You wearing his clothes</strong><br />When you put on nothing but his shirt on, it's like you're saying you can't get enough of him.</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Decode how he acts after a fight</headline><byline>Molly Triffin</byline><introtext>In a perfect world, your man would say, "Honey, I'm so sorry about what happened." But Guyville doesn't work that way. Experts translate his post-battle behaviour.</introtext><bodytext><p>In a perfect world, your man would sit you down on the couch and say,  "Honey, I'm so sorry about what happened  (even if it wasn't his fault).  But Guyville doesn't work that way. Experts translate his post-battle  behaviour.</p><p><strong> He texts you an apology</strong><br />So after an argument, he sends you a text to make up. Problem is, without hearing his voice or seeing his face when he says the S word, it's hard to tell how he's feeling. "This is a good first step. It shows that after mulling things over, he's attempting to repair the damage,  says William July, Ph.D., author of Understanding The Tin Man.<br /><br />"Although you'd probably prefer a face-to-face talk, he might be avoiding an in-person conversation because talking about his feelings isn't something he's used to.  It's easier for him to apologise via electronics, because it gives him a protective filter in case you're upset.<br /><br />But pay attention to his wording and how the text affects you emotionally when you read it. "The devil is in the details,  stresses Xavier Amador, Ph.D., author of I'm Right, You're Wrong, Now What? "If it touches a nerve and makes you feel closer to him, then that means he's genuine.  If the message falls flat and leaves you confused or distressed, you need to reach a deeper resolution with him. </p><p><strong> He seems totally normal</strong><br />You just had a blowout and your guy appears unfazed&mdash;watching the game, singing in the shower, making spaghetti. Is it opposite day? Does he have sudden-onset amnesia? There are two reasons why he'd be unruffled. "Either it wasn't that big of a deal to him,  July says, "or he is really pissed and is tuning you out. <br /><br />To tell which it is, look for little signs. Does he squeeze your waist while you're doing your make-up, send you a funny link from work, and fill you in about his day as soon as he gets home? If he's warm with you, chances are that he has gotten over it. "But if you sense distance between you, there's probably anger lurking and this is his passive-aggressive way of dealing with it,  July says.<br /><br />He might think you were in the wrong and hasn't forgiven you. Red flags: he is short when answering<br /><br />your questions, goes along with plans you make but doesn't offer any ideas of his own, or is less touchy-feely with you. If that's the case, bring up the fight casually, like while you're watching TV, so you can finally end it. <strong> </strong></p><p><strong> He wants to move on to make-up sex</strong><br />Whoa! Down, boy. The dust has hardly settled before this horn dog wants to work out the tension between the sheets. There's nothing wrong with make-up sex after you've worked through the problem, but don't use it as a Band-Aid. "He might be turning to sex as a way to ignore reality and achieve a false sense of closeness,  July explains. "However, if the dispute isn't solved, the situation will snowball and only get worse. <br /><br />He might also rush to hit the sheets because he's freaked out that the relationship could be on the rocks. "Guys have a fix-it mind-set and want to take action to make things right again,  Amador says. "He turns to you physically for reassurance that everything is okay.  Let him know that your spat doesn't mean you're breaking up and you still want to be with him. That's a nightmare for most dudes who are seriously into you. Once he feels that you're on solid ground, he'll be more open to talking. Then tell him that you do need to deal with the original issue. <strong> </strong></p><p><strong> He buys you flowers or a present</strong><br />You'd be crazy to dissuade a guy from bestowing you with roses or jewellery, right? But these goodies can be a smokescreen when a dude doesn't want to talk through a dispute.<br /><br />"Beware of gifts that aren't accompanied by a sincere apology,  July says. "No matter who was to blame, he might be tossing you a consolation prize.  If the box of chocolates came with a note reading "I love you,  probe him about how he's feeling. "Thank him, and then tell him you're still upset,  Amador says. "Yet give him the benefit of the doubt. It might have been a real gesture of regret, only he didn't know how to express it verbally. <br /><br />Also take into account how personal the gift is. "If he leaves your favourite kind of cheesecake in the fridge as a surprise, that's truly thoughtful,  July notes. "It can be a genuine peace offering for longterm couples who don't need to hash out the details of every fight.  Whereas a generic bouquet is a tactic to sweep things under the rug.</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Sex show-off</headline><byline></byline><introtext>I have a friend who constantly brags about her sex life.</introtext><bodytext><p><strong>I have a friend who constantly brags about her sex life. It's getting to the point where I can't mention the weather without her discussing a time she and her boyfriend had sex in the rain. I want her to stop because it's really annoying, but I don't want her to accuse me of being jealous. Any ideas?</strong><br />Obsessive bragging is almost always a sign of insecurity, not confidence. Say that to your friend, in so many words, and ask her why she needs to share so much information with you. Explain that it makes you uncomfortable, and you rather she kept her sex life under wraps. And on some level if you are jealous, believe me, there's no reason for it, the sex life she describes isn't reality, it's wishful thinking.</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Panty sniffer</headline><byline></byline><introtext>Whenever I stay over at my boyfriend's house, I always end up losing a pair of underwear.</introtext><bodytext><strong>Whenever I stay over at my boyfriend's house, I always end up losing a pair of underwear. Recently, I found out why when I opened my guy's drawer and spotted five pairs of my dirty panties! I asked him what was up, and he said my scent turns him on. This grosses me out. Am I being prudish?</strong><br />Scientists have begun to discover that we are more aware of basic natural odours than we realise, so your boyfriend is no doubt using his little collection to masturbate with you in mind. As long as you two have a good, hot love life together, that's not such a crime, is it? The only problem is that he may not just be sniffing your panties; it's possible that he may have a pretty common fetish for sniffing any used undies that come his way. If that's the case, I think you would be within your rights to tell him how you feel and ask him to get rid of his little secret stash. If he truly cares about you and is ready to have a serious relationship, then he should have no trouble saying goodbye to his collection. On the other hand, if he is addicted to panty sniffing, then the fetish objects themselves are more important to him than anything, even the woman who wore them. In this case, he will need therapy to find the source of his obsession and deal with the problem once and for all.</bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Bad-boy breakthrough</headline><byline></byline><introtext>I work for a large corporation that's very conservative, but I have this thing for men with tonnes of piercings and tattoos.</introtext><bodytext><strong>I work for a large corporation that's very conservative, but I have this thing for men with tonnes of piercings and tattoos. I can never bring any of my boyfriends to the office because my bosses would freak out. Should I try to get over my bad-boy fixation or expect my higher-ups to accept it?</strong><br />Don't do either. As long as you show up on time and do your job well, your private life is your own business. Why should you bring your personal pleasures to work? If you have the occasional function that requires you to attend with a date, then invite a male friend who is presentable and likely to enjoy himself at the kind of event that would probably bore your regular boyfriends. I have to wonder, though, if your decision to be with these men has more to do with feeling trapped in your day-to-day life than with attraction. It's fun straddling the fence between two worlds, but sooner or later, most of us tend to settle down on one side or the other. Maybe you need to figure out what would really make you happy, both personal l y and professionally.</bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>King Chatty</headline><byline></byline><introtext>The guy I'm seeing talks incessantly during sex. <br /> </introtext><bodytext><p><strong>The guy I'm seeing talks incessantly during sex. Worst of all, he asks me to describe how I'm feeling every second. It completely distracts me from the act itself and I can't even enjoy it. What can I do to make him stop without hurting his feelings?<br /></strong>Just like the guy who asks  Am I the best you've ever had?  after a romp, your boyfriend's need for constant verbal validation during the act might stem from insecurity about himself and his sexual performance. For whatever reason, your man needs a lot of ego stroking, so build up his confidence in every way you can. In daily life, reassure him of your respect for his opinions, ask his advice, and listen to what he says. Between the sheets, throw in some sexy sounds to help build his confidence in bed. Unfortunately, you can't exactly hit a mute button, try drowning out his voice with some sexy background music. Perhaps you could ask for some moments of silence. As his confidence in himself, and in you,kicks in, he should require less and less verbal reassurance. And if all goes well, one day, you might feel comfortable enough to say, in so many words, "Can we just shut up and do it? </p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article></section><section name="None"><article><headline>Is being too nice making you sick?</headline><byline>Zoe Ruderman</byline><introtext>Certain polite habits could land you in flu hell. It's time to ditch the niceties and stay healthy.</introtext><bodytext>We always knew that being a little bit bitchy helps you get ahead, but it turns out, it can keep you healthy too. Doctors say that certain nice-girl behaviours, like giving a sick friend a sip of your drink, can leave you with a cold, oral herpes, or swine flu. And don't assume you're safe because flu season is almost over. Swine flu, which those under 25 are particularly susceptible to, may stage a comeback this month. <br /><br />Of course, we're not advocating being downright rude. It's more about substituting a different kind of etiquette for the following practices.<br /><br /><strong>Letting someone sip your drink:</strong> Saliva is a big-time germ conductor, so avoid a potential microbe-fest on the rim of your glass by saying, "Oh, I think I feel something coming on and I don't want to make you sick. <br /><br /><strong>Kissing hello:</strong> Exchanging a quick, wet peck on the cheek can leave you with germs on your face, which can then enter your system via your nostrils or mouth. When someone goes for a smooch, lean in, air kiss, and pull back before there's any skin-on-skin contact&mdash;it lowers the odds as compared to a mouth-to-cheek connection.<br /><br /><strong>Alternating reps on gym equipment:</strong> If a fellow gym-goer asks to share the chest-press machine with you, say that you're almost done and he can have it to himself in a few. He'll likely move on to another machine while you finish, reducing the number of times his sweat and other funk from his skin.which may be crawling with bacteria, viruses, and fungi.could end up on you.<br /><br /><strong>Sharing dessert:</strong> If a pal asks to sample your confection, cut it in two, put one half on a separate plate, and joke 'If we donft split it, Ifll wolf down the whole thing!' No germs are exchanged, you save a few calories, and you come off as super generous.<br /><br /><strong>Meeting with a sick co-worker:</strong> Colds and flus thrive in offices thanks to closed windows and a lack of circulation. Avoid a face-to-face meeting by telling her that youfre chained to your desk waiting for an important call and you'd prefer to discuss things on the phone.<br /><br /><strong>Shaking someone's hand: </strong>Hands are notorious germ conveyers, but sometimes, a handshake just canft be avoided. So make sure to wash up or use hand sanitiser (always keep a minibottle in your bag) afterwards and before you touch your face.<br /><br /><strong>False confidence: </strong>Getting a flu shot and the H1N1 vaccine may leave you lax about hand washing and, therefore, more likely to spread germs.<br /><br /><strong>Sources: </strong>Etiquette Expert Melissa leonard, www.establishyourselfNY. com; Jennifer Wider, M.D., author of The Doctor's Complete College Girlsf Health Guide Source: Jennifer Wider, M.D.</bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>?Are products that enhance a guy?s performance safe??</headline><byline></byline><introtext>They may not be. These OTC pills and capsules are classified as supplements&mdash;so the FDA doesn't require them to undergo the testing that drugs do.</introtext><bodytext>They may not be. These OTC pills and capsules are classified as supplements&mdash;so the FDA doesn't require them to undergo the testing that drugs do. "They usually contain a herb called yohimbine,  says urologist Sheldon Marks, men's health expert on www.WebMD.com. "The amount of yohimbine in them is weak, but there have been reports of heart and liver problems, plus irritability and insomnia.  Warn your guy of the dangers and tell him there's no proof these concoctions actually improve satisfaction.</bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Secrets your friends know about you... That you don?t</headline><byline>Molly Triffin</byline><introtext>If there's one thing you know better than anybody, it's yourself, right? Um, no. Like most people, you're probably full of blind spots about everything, from which career is ideal for you to how you really feel about your guy. Even more shocking is who can tell you the truth. </introtext><bodytext><p>Have you ever signed on for something you didn't think you'd be crazy about and then discovered that, in fact, it was for you? Maybe a friend set you up with a guy who wasn't your type and now you're in love or a co-worker talked you&mdash;the queen of takeout&mdash;into going to her cooking class and you loved it. You're even thinking of working in a restaurant. It's weird how that happens...but what's even weirder is that someone else knew what was a good fit for you all along.<br /><br />"We're so wrapped up in ourselves that it's hard to get a clear view of who we are in certain respects,  explains Sam Gosling, Ph.D., author of Snoop: What Your Stuff Says About You. Others can step back more easily. "They see the big picture, since they don't have as much of a stake in the outcome as you do and they aren't distracted by the internal emotions that can bog you down,  says Allen McConnell, Lewis endowed professor of psychology at Miami University, in Ohio,US. All this potentially life-altering info is out there&mdash;your hidden assets and weaknesses, underutilised talents, subconscious standards for your dream guy. The techniques here will help you uncover what people around you could tell you, if you only knew how to ask.<br /><strong><br />Plumb your past</strong><br />Your innate strengths and weaknesses have likely been there all along, so your first move should be to look backward and see what people have said about you in the past. Open up your high school yearbook and read over the messages friends wrote you. What memories did they have of you? Which traits of yours did they comment on? It can also help to skim through old Facebook posts. Pay close attention to any adjectives used to describe you. Funny, stylish, wild&mdash;all these point to prominent qualities friends saw in you, the things that really stuck out about you. That information is most definitely golden.<br /><br />"We are often in the dark about what our strengths and weaknesses are when we are growing up because we're simply not aware that there's any other way to be,  Gosling explains. "For example, you might be a very talented writer, but since writing comes so naturally to you, you might not realise that you're more skilled than other people are. You simply assume everyone writes like you do. <br /><br />Use people's memories too. A great trick: ask some of your close friends or family members to tell you their favourite story about you. They might bring up moments you'd forgotten about or remember the details differently than you do, and both will clue you in to what they think is essentially you, says Simine Vazire, Ph.D., director of the Personality and Self-Knowledge Lab at Washington University, in Saint Louis,US. For example, maybe your mom remembers how you insisted on tying your shoes all by yourself with no help when you were a little kid&mdash;a sign of how independent and ambitious you were from the very start. Or your husband might bring up how on your first date with him, you gave the bartender specific instructions about how to prepare your dirty martini and he liked that you were take-charge rather than passive and knew exactly what you wanted.In fact, that's what got him hooked in the very first place. And he's been your loyal slave ever since.<br /><br /><strong>Listen for surprises</strong><br />If a person says something about you that takes you aback or doesn't jibe with how you think of yourself, don't get pissed about it&mdash;get curious. "We each have an idea of who we are and who we want to be,  Gosling says. "While this is essential to help guide us toward our goals, it can also close us down to other options that don't fit in with the picture we've created.  That naturally occurring tunnel vision can lead you to gloss over observations that contradict the vision you have of yourself. But if you don't look outside the tunnel, you might miss out on some abso-incredible opportunities. So the next time a comment someone makes surprises you, probe the person for more details about her statement. Say a friend mentions that she thinks you'd be a great match with an artsy guy she knows, even though you usually go for the sporty type. Ask her why she believes you would be a good fit.<br /><br />"She is probably picking up on a vibe that you don't notice you're giving off,  Vazire points out. It might be the case that a more free-spirited, sensitive dude would actually be a better complement to you than the frat-tastic guys you've been dating up until now.<br /><br />Pay attention, too, when there's a mismatch in how you and another person feel about something that's happening in your life. If you're telling a friend how excited you are about your plan to move to the West Coast, but her facial expression or tone of voice seems a bit doubtful or even worried, "that's a sign she might have a different point of view,  McConnell warns. While she might not necessarily know what's best for you&mdash;and it's definitely crucial to listen to your gut first and foremost&mdash;her reaction is a piece of information suggesting you might want to evaluate more carfully whether this is indeed the right decision.<br /><br /><strong>Conduct a covert poll</strong><br />One reason it's so tricky to figure out how others see you is that they're often too polite to give you straightforward feedback. "People probably won't tell you the whole truth if you ask them flat-out what they think your best and worst traits are or whether they think you're on the right career path,  Vazire says. "They'll tell you what they think you want to hear.  So you have to find a clever way to get at their honest opinions.<br /><br />The key is to casually ask friends and family members offbeat questions that will reveal who they believe you really are without their feeling that they're dissecting your personality. A few to try: "Who do you think should play me in a movie?  "Which celebrity could you most see me dating?  "What song reminds you of me?  Bring up the question nonchalantly, maybe over drinks after work, as though it's a funny thing that just popped into your head.<br /><br />Another way to go about it is to float 'trial balloons' by pals when you're considering making a change and gauge their responses. "I'm thinking of switching my major to forensic science/joining an improv group/going on safari for my honeymoon. Are you surprised?  It's a neutral question, so they should answer honestly.<br /><br />Or engage their imaginations by asking if they could picture you doing something different: "Could you see me dating a football player?  or "Could you imagine me working in the fashion world?  You'll learn a lot from their reactions&mdash;if they hesitate or seem taken aback, it's a tip-off that they don't associate those qualities with you. But if they're truly enthusiastic about this potential new venture, then you're probably onto something. <br /><br />Of course, the people in your life aren't infallible, and you don't want to follow their advice blindly while ignoring your own instincts, McConnell stresses. So find a balance between the "trees  you can see and the "forest  others might be able to discern. Be sure to take some time to pinpoint what feels right to you about a particular decision or change before seeking out other opinions. Once you're sure of that, get input from friends, coworkers, or family, and then reconsider the situation.<br /><strong><br />Connect the dots<br /></strong>You don't always have to solicit big statements to get great feedback, though. Stay attuned to some seemingly insignificant clues that can pop up at random times. For instance, look out for loaded words&mdash;superlatives like always and never. "Whenever someone uses emphatic language while talking about you, it sheds light on a strong personality trait they see in you,  Vazire notes.<br /><br />Also, watch for patterns in how people describe you. If your boyfriend mentions that you're a great public speaker after seeing you give a toast at your sister's wedding, that's certainly nice to know. But if your boyfriend, aunt, and an acquaintance you just met five minutes ago all tell you the same exact thing, then you should listen a little more carefully.<br /><br />It can be helpful to think about the role you play in people's lives as well, Vazire adds. Are you the one friends call when they're having a crisis or the one who finds out about the drama after it's already resolved? Does your boss ever ask you to spearhead a last-minute project or is a coworker usually put in charge? Assessing what people turn to you for versus what they cut you out of says something about your talents (like that you're a good listener or cool-headed under pressure) and things that you need to work on (being more empathetic, juggling multiple tasks).<br /><br />Just remember to be open to what you discover about yourself, and don't freak out if some of the secrets that you uncover are negative. Because in the end, having a fuller picture of the real you&mdash;both the good and the bad stuff&mdash; will guide you toward your most perfect job, the greatest guy for you, and your most kick-ass life. Just remember to be open to what you discover about yourself, and don't freak out if some of the secrets that you uncover are negative. So what are waiting for? Factor in some quality, listenin-about-me time with your BFF to make your life so much sweeter than it is at the moment and you'll be perenially grateful.</p><p> </p><table border="1" cellspacing="5" cellpadding="5" width="500" align="center"><tbody><tr><td><p> </p><div align="center"><strong> Your love life</strong><br /></div><br /><strong>Spot relationship truths before your friends do</strong><br /><br />Weird as it sounds, a study found that your friends are better at predicting whether your relationship will last than you are. According to researcher Christopher Agnew, Ph.D., department head and professor of psychological sciences at Purdue University, they have clearer judgment because they're less invested. But there are ways to access that info yourself&mdash;these tips will get you started.<br /><p> </p><p><br /><strong>1.</strong> 'Read' pictures of the two of you: It's tricky to be objective  about your love life. Take a step back by looking at photos as if  you're one of your friends viewing you. Consider how close you appear:  if you look like you're really into each other or if there's a definite  sense of ambivalence.<br /> <br /> <strong>2. </strong>Notice what you edit out: The details you omit when talking to  others about your man point to potential red flags. Haven't had sex in a  month? Arguing more? Maybe you're afraid it'll sound bad, but it's key  to look at these when assessing your bond.<br /> <br /> <strong>3. </strong>Compare yourself to the Joneses: Your friends see you  juxtaposed with other twosomes, so think about how you and your man  differ from couples you know: do you make more or less physical contact?  Do you smile and laugh as much as they do?<br /> <br /> <strong>4. </strong>Decode your own body language: One reason friends can read  your relationship so well is that they observe how you interact  physically. You can do the same. Signs you're solid: your feet turn  towards his; you mirror each other's movements.<br /> <br /> <strong>5. </strong>Check out old e-mails: Another thing friends observe is how  you communicate&mdash;whether your dialogue is natural and fun or strained.  Get a sense of it by going through past e-mails and G-chats. These will  give you valuable clues. </p><p><em>Source: simine vazire, ph.d.</em></p></td></tr></tbody></table></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article></section><section name="Quickies"><article><headline>Is being too nice making you sick?</headline><byline>Zoe Ruderman</byline><introtext>It's time to ditch the niceties and stay healthy. Read on.</introtext><bodytext><p>We always knew that being a little bit bitchy helps you get ahead, but it turns out, it can keep you healthy too. Doctors say that certain nice-girl behaviours, like giving a sick friend a sip of your drink, can leave you with a cold, oral herpes, or swine flu. And don't assume you're safe because flu season is almost over. Swine flu, which those under 25 are particularly susceptible to, may stage a comeback this month. Of course, we're not advocating being downright rude. It's more about substituting a different kind of etiquette for the following practices. <br /><br /><strong> KISSING HELLO<br /></strong>Exchanging a quick, wet peck on the cheek can leave you with germs on your face, which can then enter your system via your nostrils or mouth. When someone goes for a smooch, lean in, air kiss, and pull back before there's any skin-on-skin contact&mdash;it lowers the odds as compared to a mouth-to-cheek connection. <br /><br /><strong>LETTING SOMEONE SIP YOUR DRINK<br /></strong>Saliva is a big-time germ conductor, so avoid a potential microbe-fest on the rim of your glass by saying, "Oh, I think I feel something coming on and I don't want to make you sick. <br /><br /><strong>ALTERNATING REPS ON GYM EQUIPMENT<br /></strong>If a fellow gym-goer asks to share the chest-press machine with you, say that you're almost done and he can have it to himself in a few. He'll likely move on to another machine while you finish, reducing the number of times his sweat and other funk from his skin&mdash;which may be crawling with bacteria, viruses, and fungi&mdash;could end up on you.<br /><br /><strong>SHARING DESSERT<br /></strong>If a pal asks to sample your confection, cut it in two, put one half on a separate plate, and joke "If we don't split it, I'll wolf down the whole thing!  No germs are exchanged, you save a few calories, and you come off as super generous.<br /><br /><strong>MEETING WITH A SICK CO-WORKER<br /></strong>Colds and flus thrive in offices thanks to closed windows and a lack of circulation. Avoid a face-to-face meeting by telling her that you're chained to your desk waiting for an important call and you'd prefer to discuss things on the phone. <br /><br /><strong>SHAKING SOMEONE'S HAND<br /></strong>Hands are notorious germ conveyers, but sometimes, a handshake just can't be avoided. So make sure to wash up or use hand sanitiser (always keep a minibottle in your bag) afterwards...and before you touch your face.</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article></section><section name="You..."><article><headline>The Cosmo girl works like this!</headline><byline>Pratishtha Dobhal</byline><introtext>Not all old school theories need to be trashed &mdash; Just these 8 here! Read on for complete details inside.</introtext><bodytext><p>Permanence of a state of being is as boring as sporting a hairstyle that whisked out of fashion a decade ago. As is getting stuck in a moment of comfort at the same workplace forever and ever, and ever...zzzz. While skeptics, rationalists, and old school (your folks mostly) worked a certain way, the very Cosmo, very 'with-it' girl moves up the ladder, bending the old school rules to work in her favour. Mommy didn't guide us wrong, we just interpreted it a whole new way in 2010. Register, write, reflect and read right here! <br /><br /><strong> Don't crank &mdash; work with deeper focus<br />OLD SCHOOL: </strong>The old school of productivity taught us how to crank out the tasks. Each task is a widget that needs to be cranked and the more we crank out, the better. Speed is important, and cranking out more tasks is the ultimate criteria. How many tasks can you finish in a day?<br /><br /><strong>NEW SCHOOL: </strong>The new worker isn't as obsessed with speed but with finishing the task at hand. This allows for a new kind of productivity&mdash;one where quality matters, amazing things are produced at an intense rate and you are satisfied with the end result.<br /><br /><strong>Minimise out meetings and planning&mdash;just start<br />OLD SCHOOL: </strong>Lots of planning is important. Hold numerous planning meetings, draw up specs or detailed timelines.<br /><br /><strong>NEW SCHOOL: </strong>Just start. Forget all the detailed planning. Meetings are a waste of time, usually. Instead, figure out the minimum requirements to launch, get those done as quickly as possible, and launch in beta mode. Finesse comes later&mdash;getting started is the real challenge.<br /><br /><strong>Paperwork is out &mdash; Automate with technology<br />OLD SCHOOL: </strong>DD programs made files on the desk synonymous with being overburdened and stuck in a rut. Our previous generation didn't get cntrl+alt+delete. Lucky we!<br /><br /><strong>NEW SCHOOL: </strong>Automate with technology. Many workers are learning to go paperless. And because everything is becoming digital, you can use technology to process it faster. Your overseas boss can be given roses on a bad day&mdash;now we are talking!<br /><br /><strong>Don't multitask &mdash; Multi-Project and single-task<br />OLD SCHOOL: </strong>Multi-tasking is productive. Juggling tasks shows how productive you are.<br /><br /><strong>NEW SCHOOL: </strong>Multi-project and single-task. If working on Task 1 of Project A&mdash;you should single-task while working on Task 1. But when it's done, you might need to wait for a response from your boss before moving to Task 2. In that case, while you're waiting, you can work on Task 1 of Project B, single-tasking while doing that. The end result: consistency instead of chaos.<br /><br /><strong>Produce less, not more<br />OLD SCHOOL: </strong>Good managers tried to get as much productivity out of their workers as possible. Good workers produced more.<br /><br /><strong>NEW SCHOOL: </strong>More isn't always better. The old thinking can lead to a big pile of crap. Instead, focus on quality, on innovation and creativity. The biggest blockbuster of 2010&mdash;3 Idiots&mdash;was the result of four years of meticulously working on a script, unlike a run-of-the-mill dud movie. Think Aamir Khan. Make yourself indispensible. <br /><br /><strong>Forget about organisation &mdash; use technology<br />OLD SCHOOL: </strong>Be organised. The productive worker of the past had drawers full of files, all organised thoroughly so that nothing would ever be lost. Much ado about nothing?<br /><br /><strong>NEW SCHOOL: </strong>Tag, archive, and search. With technology, that's not necessary. Tag a file with a certain label, archive it, and find it later through its label or through search. This approach saves a lot of time, a lot of effort, and a lot of headaches. You can spend your time on more important tasks. <br /><br /><strong>Out with hierarchies &mdash; In with freedom<br />OLD SCHOOL: </strong>Hierarchies require a lot of top-down decision-making and a lot of up-and-down communication. The bottom level is often left powerless to act until the top level makes decisions, and the top level is often left without important information necessary to make those decisions.<br /><br /><strong>NEW SCHOOL: </strong>Independence, freedom, and collaboration. Hierarchies are being flattened out. In fact, whole new forms of organisation and collaboration are being created all the time. People, more and more, are working independently, either within a company or as consultants. <br /><br /><strong>Work fixed hours. No more<br />OLD SCHOOL: </strong>Work longer hours. Work long and hard! Be a top producer! Burn out by age 40! Working long hours earned you points with your boss, and there was a competition to see who worked the most and the hardest.<br /><br /><strong>NEW SCHOOL: </strong>Work fewer hours. With more freedom, workers are realising that work isn't everything, and that it's more important to be happy, to produce important work, to have the freedom to be creative and innovative, to be passionate about your work ...than to give everything you have for something you don't care about. The author of Change The World: How Ordinary People Can Achieve Extraordinary Results, Robert E. Quinn, outlines eight steps each of us can take to move ourselves and others to the highest levels of excellence. Work can satisfy you when it is inner-directed and outerfocussed, unless you want to be stuck in an endless time warp.  Need we say more?</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Curb cravings without eating a thing</headline><byline></byline><introtext>Do you ever find yourself reaching for a high-calorie food when you shouldn't even be hungry?</introtext><bodytext><p>Do you ever find yourself reaching for a high-calorie food when you  shouldn't even be hungry? Turns out, the human brain has a tendency to  fire off a "I need to eat  message in response to emotions and  situations that have nothing to do with appetite...and constantly  misreading that cue and chowing down can pack on extra pounds. The trick  is to learn what your body is trying to tell you and what kind of fix  your system truly needs. These tips will help you avoid loads of  calories in the easiest way possible.<br /><br /><strong>You're stressed<br /> </strong>It's human nature to crave a reward for hard work. So when you're  under a lot of pressure&mdash;for example, you need to finish a big project at  your job&mdash;you start fantasising about getting some sweet payback for  your extra effort. But while you might want to get a luxe massage or  blow off work and hang with friends, those kinds of things require free  time, which is in short supply on tense days.<br /><br />Food, on the other  hand, is an almost instant reward, especially if you get it by  speed-eating through the fridge or racing out to the nearest  drive-through. It's such a natural way to pamper yourself that  nutritionists say many women subconsciously start to associate feeling  overwhelmed or overworked with a trip to the vending machine or a plate  of soaked-in-oil fries.<br /><br />Scarfing all that junk won't really  satisfy you, though. When you're stressed, you're actually less likely  to savour the taste of your food or respond to feelings of fullness. So  pop in a piece of gum instead. It can help in two ways: some experts  claim that chewing is calming and you'll sidestep those calories that  you wouldn't have even enjoyed anyway.<br /><br /><strong>You're exhausted<br /> </strong>Ever notice that you're desperate for sugary and carb-loaded foods  after a bad (or short) night of sleep? That's because when you're  dragging, your body craves a jolt of energy...and a sweet snack often  delivers an instant boost.<br /><br />Thing is, not only does your body not  need the calories, but indulging in something sweet and junky will  actually make you feel more tired, since sugar-energy highs are followed  by rapid energy plunges. Instead, wake yourself up when you're feeling  beat with a quick burst of exercise&mdash;for example, a 20-minute gym routine  or a brisk walk. Then plan to better manage your fatigue next time, by  either getting to bed half an hour earlier or taking a much-needed power  nap.<br /><br /><strong>You worked out<br /> </strong>Exercising depletes your body's protein, which may explain why you  sometimes want to chow down on cheese or meat right after clocking time  on the treadmill. But that craving doesn't mean you have to eat a mega  meal. Instead of inhaling hundreds of calories (and negating the hard  work you put in at the gym), satisfy your protein need by drinking a  glass of non-fat milk. Eight ounces has just 86 calories but enough  protein to quell your urges till it's time for lunch or dinner.<br /><strong><br /> You're near other noshers</strong><br />You feel full after a satisfying  dinner...but then you show up at a friend's party and start grazing. The  environmental cues (food spread out on a table, people's mouths  munching) and our innate human desire to mimic others are making you  think you're hungry when you aren't. So keep your hands and mouth  otherwise engaged.for instance, by grabbing a seltzer or just chatting  and flirting (anything that keeps your mouth busy).<br /><br /><strong>You're  bumming</strong><br />As kids, we're often placated by our parents and teachers  with yummy treats, which may be why we connect those same foods (often  sweets) with getting out of a funk. Think of how many times your mom  said 'Here, have a cookie' to stop your crying. But what you really need  when you're feeling blue is emotional comfort from someone close to  you. So rather than reaching for a cupcake, reach for your cellphone or  your laptop and call a friend or cruise Facebook.<br /><br />It also helps  to get energetic: experts say connecting with other people and getting  out of your apartment and doing something. even if it's window-shopping  with friends. banishes bad-mood hunger.<br /><br /><strong>You're procrastinating</strong><br />Women  often eat to delay making a tough decision or to put off an unwanted  task. Nutritionists say we tend to choose food over things like watching  TV or going online because those types of activities seem like a waste  of time and 'real' procrastination, whereas eating doesn't since, hey, a  girl's gotta eat. Stop kidding yourself and either give in to goofing  off or buckle down and get it done. At least you won't have to feel  guilty about being unproductive and overeating.<br /><br /><strong>You're thirsty</strong><br />Hunger  and thirst fire off nearly identical messages in the brain, so our  bodies often confuse the need to drink with the need to eat. If you ate  recently but are suddenly jonesing for some solid sustenance, the  explanation is probably dehydration. That's why nutritionists say the  first thing to do when you're craving food is drink water. Guzzle it  down, and wait about 10 minutes; that lingering hunger will probably  fade.<br /><br /><strong>You're bored<br /></strong>We migrate to the kitchen when we  have nothing to do because, well, it's something to do.something fun and  pleasurable to boot. If you can't get out of the house or away from  your desk and you start fantasising about chips, ice cream, or [insert  your poison here], do something competitive, like playing a video or  online game. It'll entertain you and keep your hands too busy to reach  for food.<br /><br /><em>Sources: Dawn Jackson Blatner, RD, Author of The  flexitarian diet; Jana Klauer, MD, Author of the park avenue  nutritionist's plan</em></p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>The secret lives of financially fab females</headline><byline>Rashi Wadhera</byline><introtext>What they're doing that you're not!</introtext><bodytext><p><strong> </strong>Are you envious of girls who live fabulously but still manage to not declare bAnkruptcy? We find out what they're doing that you're not!<br /><strong><br /> Diva Driver</strong><br />1. Store only essentials in the trunk. Heavy objects add to weight and decrease mileage<br /><br />2. When buying a second-hand car, opt for cars coming straight off leases, meaning they were cared for by dependable owners.<br /><br />3, Check if tyres are inflated properly. Under-inflated tyres result in extra fuel consumption and wear out faster.<br /><br /><strong> The Great Housekeeper<br /></strong>1. Buy appliances based on reliability, not what's cheapest at the store.<br /><br />2. Do a price comparison&mdash;find a cheaper grocery store. Keep track of the things you buy most, shop for these items at a couple of stores, one will come out most economical.</p><p> </p><p> </p><p> </p><p><strong> The Shameless Splurger<br /></strong>1. We know you're generous but shop-bought presents are not economical. You can make food, candles, cards at home which are both inexpensive and personal. So while everyone is tearing up about how thoughtful your present was, pat yourself on the back for money well saved!<br /><br />2. Always have alternative money making methods&mdash; wedding choreographer, freelance wrtiting. You can indulge anticipating cash flow.<br /><br />3. Trawl your cellphone bills and cancel any services you don't use but are paying rental for.<br /><br />4. Make a separate fund for all your lavish indulges putting money in it periodically. <br /><br /><strong> Confessions of a Shopaholic<br /></strong>1. Will that be cash, cheque or credit card? Your answer should always be cash; that way you stay clear of credit card debt and can't spend more than you have!<br /><br />2. Factory outlets make the most sense; maybe not for a statement look, but for essentials head to a factory outlet for the best prices.<br /><br />3. If you're a girl into fashion with a limited budget (who isn't?), focus on buying timeless, classic clothing. You'll have to shop less often.</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Learn to love the suckiest day of week</headline><byline>Mina Azodi</byline><introtext>New research has pinpointed the crappiest 24 hours. If you tweak your routine in some KEY WAYS, you might actually start to look forward to it.</introtext><bodytext><p>There's no doubt about it: Mondays are tough. But according to new research, Wednesdays can really suck the life out of you...literally. A recent study found that most suicides occur mid-week. "It's the tipping point,  says Augustine Kposowa, Ph.D., the study author and professor at the University of California at Riverside. "Stress from Monday and Tuesday weighs people down and the weekend can still feel very far away. <br /><br /><strong> </strong>Okay, the study looked at the worst-case scenario, but it gets at a truth that has intensified since the recession: people are working harder and spending less on breaks like happy hour, which makes for less, well, happiness. But it doesn't take a lot of time or money to get your week (and mood) back on track. Try these tactics for quick relief. <br /><br /><strong>1.</strong> Have a quickie in the morning, even if it's solo, so you get that feel-good cocktail of oxytocin and dopa mine into your system. After all, they do call it, uh, hump day.<br /><br /><strong>2.</strong> Sprinkle some cinnamon in your morning coffee. Not only will it dress up your java, but a study found that the scent also can decrease anxiety and stimulate the part of your brain tasked with keeping you alert.<br /><br /><strong>3.</strong> Nix the brown bag and make this your lunching-out day. It's a small change, but trying new things&mdash;even simply a different deli&mdash;will spark an adrenaline rush that helps to fuel a good mood.<br /><br /><strong>4.</strong> Create a Wednesday a.m. playlist for your commute. Bumper-to-bumper traffic isn't so bad when you're blast ing your fave songs.<br /><br /><strong>5.</strong> Sign up for www. astrologyzone.com, a horoscope site. Choose to have the info sent to you on Wed nes days. It's unlikely that they'll ever put anything to make you feel like you are down in the dumps. It should serve as a happy shot.<br /><br /><strong>6.</strong> Schedule your Saturday plans now and the weekend won't feel so far off. Or plan the details of another event&mdash;an upcoming concert or vacation. Just imagining yourself lounging on a beach is an instant mental holiday.<br /><br /><strong>7.</strong> Make Wednesday Would You Rather Day with your guy. Exchange texts like "Would you rather I kiss your thigh or your neck?  Anticipating each other's texts will make the day speed by and give you great ammo for a hot hook-up later.<br /><br /><strong>8.</strong> Buy an inexpensive flower to put on your desk, like a daisy or a rose. Certain colours can improve your mood&mdash;including yellow, which boosts happiness and red, which amps excitement.<br /><br /><strong>9.</strong> Change your desktop background to a fun pic from a recent day off (just right-click a cute photo from one of your friends' Facebook albums). It'll be a visual reminder of the good times you have coming your way in less than 72 hours.</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Your decorating dilemmas solved</headline><byline></byline><introtext>Eric Cohler, an interior designer in New York City who can make any room look great, comes to the rescue.</introtext><bodytext><p>Eric Cohler, an interior designer in New York City who can make any room  look great, comes to the rescue. </p><p><strong>Q:</strong> I can't afford a headboard for my bed. How do I lose the dorm look?<br /><strong>A:</strong> Paint a headboard! It is cheap and takes no time at all. Choose a colour that complements your bedding, and paint a large rectangle right above where your bed sits. With a contrasting colour, paint a 3- to 4-inch border around the rectangle.<br /><br /><strong>Q:</strong> I have a bunch of photos I want to display. Any suggestions on how?<br /><strong>A:</strong> Order varying sizes of prints from redcover.com/Getty Images Eric Cohler, an interior designer in New York City who can make any room look great, comes to the rescue. your local photo shop. Then invest in the same frame in different sizes and hang them in groups. If you want the display to be really fancy, pick frames that have mats in them.<br /><br /><strong>Q: </strong>What's a simple way to make my puny space appear bigger?<br /><strong>A:</strong> Most people stay away from darkcoloured paint, but if you use a deep hue on only your ceiling or one wall, it helps it recede, making the room seem larger. Also, use touches of light colours everywhere else (throws, vases, artwork, etc.) to make the area feel alive and airy.<br /><br /><strong>Q: </strong>I like the look of a centrepiece on my dining table or coffee table, but flowers die. What lasts?<br /><strong>A:</strong> Buy a large glass vase (they're cheap at your local flea market), and fill it with sand or moss balls. You can also set out one or a stack of pretty photo albums on a coffee table&mdash;they're fun for guests to flip through. Colourful candles are always a good idea too.<br /><br /><strong>Q:</strong> I have a duvet cover and my blanket gets all bunched up in it. How can I keep it smooth?<br /><strong>A: </strong>You can find weighted clips at certain convenience stores . Secure them to all four sides of the comforter before slipping it inside the duvet cover.<br /><br /><strong>Q:</strong> My parents gave me their old,ugly couch. How can I try to modernise it?<br /><strong>A: </strong>Shop for a simple slipcover&mdash;you can find really inexpensive ones now. Choose a colour that goes with the room or opt for white or beige. If it gets dirty, you can just bleach it. Then dress it up with unique pillows.</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>When breasts don?t match</headline><byline></byline><introtext>The scoop on three common variations.</introtext><bodytext><p>The scoop on three common variations.</p><p><strong>One breast is bigger than the other</strong><br />This is usually the case whether you notice it or not and it's not unheard of or abnormal for one breast to be up to half a cup larger than the other. If your size difference makes you feel selfconscious, wear a padded bra so your breasts appear to be more even. Be concerned if one breast suddenly grows larger. In this case, see your doc.<br /><br /><strong>Your nipples point in different directions</strong><br />One might point up while the other points down, left, or right. It depends on where the areola rests on each breast&mdash;for example, if the areola sits higher on one of your breasts, it may angle the nipple upward.<br /><strong><br />Each breast has a different shape</strong><br />Even if your girls are the same cup size, they are likely to hang differently. This could happen if your workouts favour one side of your body, because the muscle on that side gets more toned, and the breast above it looks more prominent. Again, if one suddenly looks different from the other, check in with your M.D.<br /><br /><em>Source: Jennifer Wider, m.d., Women's Health Specialist and Cosmo Radio Health Expert</em></p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>No more period pains</headline><byline></byline><introtext>Fast solutions to the misery your flow brings</introtext><bodytext><p>Fast solutions to the misery your flow brings</p><p><strong>Killer cramps:</strong> When you sense your period is imminent, be pro-active and take two anti-inflammatory painkillers every four to six hours. This should work to prevent crampcausing chemicals from being released.<br /><br /><strong>Achy, tender breasts:</strong> Ease the bloating that makes breast tissue sensitive this difficult time of the month by avoiding caffeine and salty foods&mdash;both cause your system to retain water.<br /><strong><br />Diarrhoea and/or gas:</strong> Digestive discomfort during the first days are the result of the same body chemicals that cause cramps. Bland foods, such as bananas and rice, can reduce tummy trouble.<br /><br /><em>Source: Rae cherng, ob-gyn in san jose, california,us</em></p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Unleash your inner Telly diva</headline><byline>Priyanka Chowdhury</byline><introtext>Can't get enough of the idiot box? Don't fret. Your addiction to Friday blockbusters might help you achieve your hidden potential. Cosmo decodes the secret benefits of being a soap opera junkie.</introtext><bodytext><p>W've all lusted after Rachel's bangs, Carrie's shoes, and Summer's boyfriend. To soothe the green-eyed monster slightly, we tell ourselves it's only the Jennifer Anistons, SJPs, and Rachel Bilsons of the world who have the prerogative to look and be that smokin'. However, there's far more to these iconic characters than the gorgeous women who bring them to life. And guess what? You could be just as sensational. Cosmo clues you in to a few subtle changes of smallscreen goddesses that'll transform you into a true blue telly diva.<br /><br /><strong>Realise your inner Rachel</strong><br />Rachel Green (a.k.a Jennifer Aniston) makes her first appearance in the pilot episode of Friends in a wedding dress. This runaway bride leaves her groom stranded at the altar after she figures she likes the prezzies more than the Prince Charming. Despite her superrich parents' disdain, she shacks up with BFF Monica and learns to love, live, and pay her bills in the big, bad world.<br /><br /><strong>Why the world loves her:</strong> She's goofy, sexy, can make sackcloth look nice as couture, and ups the fossil-lovin' Ross Gellar's dude-factor by many degrees. She's not afraid to date the wrong men or to break up with the love of her life when he cheats on her after a fight. Her turbulent, now-on-now-off affair with Ross, before the two end up together at the end of the series, is the stuff of legend. Plus, her tresses have made hairstyle history across the world.<br /><br /><strong>Why cosmo salutes her:</strong> Here's a woman who's not afraid to speak her mind even when she knows she might upset someone's applecart (or, in this case, Ross's wedding with Emily). Instead of Daddy's dollars she makes her living as a waitress. She converts her flair for fashion into a rocking career. And let's not forget the elan with which she takes on the role of a single mother. Witty, brave, and strikingly beautiful, Rachel Green is definitely a fave FFF. Comes as no surprise that she gets to snog Bruce Willis, does it? Sigh...<br /><br /><strong>Diva traits to cop:</strong> Honesty, loyalty, and fearlessness.<br /><br /><strong>Carry forward like Carrie</strong><br />What can one say about Sarah Jessica Parker's rendition of Carrie Bradshaw on the cult HBO series Sex And The City that hasn't been said already? The spunky, mad-about-Manolos beauty writes a regular column for the fictional New York Star and immortalises the pleasures and pitfalls of single living in Manhattan.<br /><br /><strong>Why the world loves her:</strong> She's every shopaholic's envy with her fetish for expensive footwear, which she terms her "substance abuse problem . Her mini-celeb status as a risque columnist grants her access to every 'it' place in NYC. There's no shortfall of superstuds&mdash; Carrie's mastered the art of acquiring arm candy with ease. Then there's her often sexual, always flirtatious, and abso-challenging relationship with Mr Big. And did we forget the three Superwomen who stick by her through it all?<br /><br /><strong>Why cosmo salutes her:</strong> Carrie brought women's issues with men, commitment, and sex into the spotlight. Unapologetic about her sexual needs, at the same time she also unabashedly admits she's on an endless search for true love, and refuses to settle for "anything less than butterflies.  Her talent for social commentary helps in landing a book deal that catapults her into the big league. She might buy a fashion mag, instead of dinner, but her babelicious banter cloaks an incisive mind which seeks to identify and articulate the mind of the single, successful, Manhattan Everywoman. In 2009, The Guardian named Bradshaw as an icon of the decade, stating that "Carrie Bradshaw did as much to shift the culture around certain women's issues as real-life female groundbreakers.  To top it all, she made Cosmopolitans the preferred tipple for every FFF.<br /><br /><strong>Diva traits to cop:</strong> Love for the job, ability to follow your dreams, and celebrating imperfections.<br /><br /><strong>Step up Summer style</strong><br />Summer Roberts (played by Rachel Bilson) was the stereotypical Newport kid in her first few appearances on The O.C.&mdash;pretty, rich, and an utter snob. She dates boys on the basis of their bucks, idolises daddy, and is best friends with the leading lady, the troubled Marisa Cooper (Mischa Barton). Summer's character was supposed to feature in just a few episodes, but the superficially bitchy yet blessedwith-a-heart-of-gold babe touched a distinct chord with the audience.<br /><br /><strong>Why the world loves her: </strong>She's got tremendous spunk and once you scratch the surface, her priorities are water-tight&mdash;she tides Marisa through her bad phases, has a fantastic relationship with Seth Cohen (Adam Brody), and is unfazed by the presence of the pill-popping "Stepmonster . Summer's in-yourface attitude is a refreshing change from the usual teen angst.<br /><br /><strong>Why cosmo salutes her: </strong>It's never easy to change yourself but Summer, despite her youth, seems to instinctively veer towards transformation. She goes from being a brat to a personable young woman. Despite her defined sense of right and wrong, she's sensitive enough to back down if things aren't going her way. What's more, she's not afraid of admitting her flaws, like her constant worry that she may not be smart enough for geeky, comic-book-loving Cohen. She survives heartbreak, her best friend's death, and moves on to become an environmentalist. Her moment of triumph: fighting for Seth's love in a Wonder Woman outfit. So what if she lost the battle initially; she still made an indelible impact on his heart and ours.<br /><br /><strong>Diva traits to cop:</strong> Being dignified in defeat, balancing love and a career, and acknowledging as well as overcoming your disadvantages.</p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article><article><headline>Whoa! Were you just compliminsulted?</headline><byline>Rashi Wadhera</byline><introtext>Praise isn't always what it's cut out to be! </introtext><bodytext><p>We've all had our fair share of compliments. So much so that we've perfected our acceptance faces&mdash;a practiced smile, the flushed cheeks, and... SORRY? What the hell was that? Were you getting ready for a pat on the back and got bitch-slapped instead? Relax, you've just been compliminsulted. Here's a list of 31 back-handed compliments Cosmo readers received! Warning: before you bat those lashes in apparent humility...Listen!<br /><br /><strong>1.</strong> While driving my dreamy crush to run an errand he says "You're a damn good driver... for a woman.  <br /><em>&mdash;Sahiba,21</em><br /><br /><strong>2. </strong>At an official dinner, while I sat preening, one of my subordinates came up to me and said "Your boyfriend is dreamy... How did you guys end up together?  <br /> <em>&mdash;Shagun, 21</em><br /><br /><strong>3.</strong> My mother at her usual embarassing best, says to me at a family reunion "That dress is very flattering on you... really hides your flabby midriff, you should thank your stars.  <br /><em>&mdash;Neha, 24</em><br /><br /><strong>4. </strong>One of my bitchy co-workers at work sought me out to say "Your sweater is to die for! It really hides your double chin.  <br /><em>&mdash;Richa, 25</em><br /><br /><strong>5. </strong>Being hit on at a club, my ability to keep up with conversation gave one of the guys the perfect opening to say "You're a lot smarter than you look you know!  <br /><em>&mdash;Naina, 22</em><br /><br /><strong>6. </strong>My maternal aunt, at my congratulatory dinner, announced at the time of my toast "Congratulations on getting into such a good school after you tried so hard. I didn't think you were that smart!  <br /><em>&mdash;Aditi, 21</em><br /><br /><strong>7. </strong>"You have the greatest untapped potential of anyone I have ever slept with.  My hottest booty call yet says this to me&mdash;total buzz kill! <br /><em>&mdash;Sahil, 21</em><br /><br /><strong>8. </strong>Probing my girlfriend for her description of our latest romp, she had me wishing I never asked when she said "Relax baby, your sexual performance was perfectly adequate for someone in a new relationship. I am sure we'll 'get there' soon enough.  <br /><em>&mdash;Arjun, 22</em><br /><br /><strong>9. </strong>My pesky little pre-teen niece, having just discovered hair removal, thought it was a compliment when she said "Those blackheads form the cutest pattern!  <br /><em>&mdash;Ankita, 23</em><br /><br /><strong>10. </strong>While desperately trying to help my hot new co-worker to access Facebook at work, she nonchalantly says "How persistent you are... most people would have called someone competent by now.  I was hoping for a very different kind of reward! <br /><em>&mdash;Raghav, 22</em><br /><br /><strong>11.</strong> Once I was offstage after one of my plays, a lady walked up to me and said "Oh dear, aren't you brave to do that?  <br /><em>&mdash;Sanjana, 19</em><br /><strong><br />12. </strong>My boyfriend's deranged ex looked me up and down and belittled me while hundreds watched saying "Wow a tight, short LBD? You have great confidence in your inner beauty.  <br /><em>&mdash;Urvika, 28</em><br /><br /><strong>13.</strong> My date, who had the IQ of a squirrel, actually thought he was being funny when he quipped "You really make me feel intelligent baby, especially when you talk.  <br /><em>&mdash;Sonali, 32</em><br /><br /><strong>14. </strong>On meeting my BFF after two years&mdash;"Look at how much weight you have lost. You look so much better in this dress compared to that last wedding you wore it to sweetheart!  <br /><em>&mdash;Archana, 27</em><br /><br /><strong>15. </strong>My delicious date's younger brother sized me up and said "It's really great you can wear such tight pants without that ugly bulge at the crotch most men have. <br /><em>&mdash;Aftab, 21</em><br /><br /><strong>16.</strong> Lying naked with a total babe, just about to get laid, my libido suddenly plunged when I heard "Ok lets try it...one that size couldn't possibly be painful.  <br /><em>&mdash;Kabir, 26</em><br /><br /><strong>17. </strong>I'm still rethinking my friendship with my best friend after I heard "I love your new haircut...I have to get the number of your stylist, she really knows how to add volume to limp hair. When can I get it?  <br /><em>&mdash;Monica, 22</em><br /><br /><strong>18. </strong>On getting professional make-up for an important night out, my friend said, "I hardly recognised you when you came . <br /><em>&mdash;Tara, 21</em><br /><br /><strong>19. </strong>My new job at a magazine didn't last very long when the art director turned to me and said "This picture of you is breath-taking...And the best part is we can photoshop those wrestler arms right out!  <br /><em>&mdash;Suhani, 28</em><br /><br /><strong>20.</strong> A reaction to my banging new body&mdash; "I'm fascinated with how good you look now, you must have been pretty hefty to begin with from the start.  <br /><em>&mdash;Meher, 24</em><br /><br /><strong>21. </strong>After showing off my new moves at a party recently&mdash;"You're such an amazing dancer which comes as a relief given your poor cooking skills!  <br /><em>&mdash;Rashi, 22</em><br /><br /><strong>22.</strong> My mom's reaction to my week-old girlfriend recently took me by surprise&mdash;"She's so pretty. And she's definitely prettier than anyone I thought you could ever come to date!  <br /><em>&mdash;Karan, 21</em><br /><br /><strong>23. </strong>Someone took the time to message me on FB saying "I love your profile picture... are you the one on the right or left?  <br /><em>&mdash;Gauri, 29</em><br /><br /><strong>24. </strong>After returning sun-kissed from a vacation in the Maldives, my sister said "I really envy your jetsetting life, how you can always just pack up and travel. Do you have a sugar daddy or something?  <br /><em>&mdash;Smriti,24</em><br /><strong><br />25.</strong> My boss greeted me Monday morning with "You look really good today...glad to see you're finally sleeping enough. Those dark circles were beginning to look like the before of a really bad infomercial.  <br /><em>&mdash;Kajal,27</em><br /><br /><strong>26. </strong>At a client meeting while presenting what I thought was genius, I was told: "Don't get me wrong&mdash;I love that you try and sound intelligent when you talk.  <br /><em>&mdash;Medha,31</em><br /><br /><strong>27. </strong>At a club with my boyfriend&mdash; "Look at the girl. She looks like a younger version of you.  <br /><em>&mdash;Prachi, 28</em><br /><br /><strong>28. </strong>My satisfaction at just having scored with a hot girl I had recently met was taken away in a micro second when I heard "It's safe to say that was my best orgasm ever&mdash;and to think I almost wrote you off thanks to your lack of conversation skills. Whew! What a relief  <br /><em>&mdash;Rohan, 22</em><br /><br /><strong>29.</strong> I was sitting smug knowing I had just fully satisified my date, anticipating a slew of compliments. She turns to me and says "You really know how to work it down there, and not being able to see your face really helped!  <br /><em>&mdash;Akul, 21</em><br /><br /><strong>30. </strong>On my latest splurge&mdash;"You look really good; most people can't pull off a dress that went out of fashion three seasons ago!  <br /><em>&mdash;Saudamini, 29</em><br /><br /><strong>31.</strong> After gloating to my crew about a hot date I had lined up, she walks in and almost screams across the restaurant, "I'm so glad you accepted this date, all my original plans fell through. I was so scared I'd have nothing to do tonight!  <br /><em>&mdash;Adit, 21</em></p></bodytext><copyright>Reproduced From Cosmopolitan. © 2010. LMIL. All rights reserved.</copyright></article></section></items></root>